(Sheldon:)He still hasn't responded.
(Sheldon:)What's taking him so long?
Do you really want
him to write back?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I do.
No matter how he responds,
(Sheldon:)I am going to destroy him
with a picture of a bored cat
saying, "Oh, really?"
(Sheldon:)Me-wow.
(Howard:)What are you doing?
(Raj:)I've, uh, created some
other user accounts
(Raj:)so I can post positive
comments about their paper.
"This wee li'l bairn
of a theory
nearly blew my kilt off"?
(Raj:)No. You have to read it
how Dr. Angus McDoogal
(Raj:)of the University
of Edinburgh would.
(Scottish accent):
"This wee li'l bairn of a theory
nearly blew me kilt off."
(gasps)
He wrote back!
"Cooper and Hofstadter resorting
to juvenile attempts at humor
"is proof they have nothing to
back up their ridiculous paper.
"It should come
as no surprise
"given they work at Cal Tech,
essentially a technical school,